Is there a fetish?
性癖ってあります?
It's a secret.
秘密です
Is it a secret?
秘密ですか?
good
好
What type of man do you like?
き な男性のタイプは?
How does it feel?
どう いった感じなんでしょうか?
Someone you feel comfortable with?
一緒にいて落ち着く人?
Is it me?
私ですか?
I can't tell you that.
そこを教えないですね
Which do you prefer, younger or older?
年下、年上はどっちが好きですか?
I prefer older people.
年上の方がいいです
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Lately, when?
最近ね、いつ
But you can go.
でも 行けるんですね
Thank you for coming again.
また来てくれてありがとうございます
Didn't you hate it last time?
この前嫌じゃなかったですか?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
TRUE?
本当?
Yes, it's okay.
はい、大丈夫です
I'm glad to hear you say that.
そう言ってくれると嬉しいけどね
She's fair-skinned, after all.
色白いですね、やっぱり
is that so?
そうですか?
It's beautiful, after all.
綺麗ですね、やっぱり
What do you think?
どう ですか?
Is it starting soon?
もうそろそろ始まりますか?
Boyfriend, please don't make it.
彼氏、作らないようにしてくださいね
In my work, there are quite a lot of people who quit after getting a boyfriend.
僕の作品、結構彼氏ができてやめていく人多いんで
I agree.
そうですね
It often occurs in cute children.
可愛い子に多いんですよ
It's not cute so it's okay.
可愛くないんで大丈夫です
No, no, what are you going to do?
いやいやいや、何をしちゃうの?
It's evil.
邪気ですよ
It was on land.
陸上でした
Ah, I see.
ああ、なるほどね
That's why you shake it on your leg muscles?
だから足筋に振るの?
No, no, no.
いやいやいや
Let's call it a calf.
ふくらはぎとするんだよ
No, not at all.
いや、全然
It fell a lot.
大分落ちました
I'd like to ask you something.
ちょっと聞きたいんですけどね
yes.
はい
What type of man do you like?
好きな男性のタイプは、どういった感じなんでしょうか?
Someone you can be with and feel at ease with.
一緒にいて落ち着く人
Is it me?
私ですか?
Maybe so.
そうかもしれないですね
Do you prefer being younger or older?
歳下、歳上はどっちが好きですか?
Older people are better.
歳上の方がいいです
Is it true?
本当ですか?
yes.
はい
I think it's about 10.
10くらいですかね
It was off.
はずれていましたね
3 sizes please.
3サイズお願いします
picture?
え?
3 sizes please.
3サイズのお願いいたします
3 sizes?
3サイズ?
yes.
はい
Have you ever found out?
分かったことはない?
That's it.
それだよ
Do you know your height and weight?
身長と体重は分かります?
Lately, when have we had sex?
最近ね、いつセック
vinegar?
ス?
Every 2 weeks.
2週 間毎回
Do you have any sexual tendencies?
なんか、性癖ってあります?
It's a secret.
秘密です
秘密ですから
During the shoot, I woke up, stood up,
撮影中に、 目覚めさせて、 立ちて、
I would like to visit.
参りたいと思います
You feel bad, man.
気分悪いね、君
is that so?
そうですか?
You, this is no good.
君、これは、 ダメだよ、これ
If you use a brush like this, it will be stolen.
こんなブラシでじゃあ、 盗まれるよ、
this.
これ
Wake up, then.
起きて、じゃあ
Can I withstand it?
耐えれるかな?
It's tightened already.
締めてるね、もう
Not tightened.
締めてない